Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 1707 Records WAG.298
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series IV: Officers and Staff-Administrative Files, 1962-2004
  - Subseries IV:B: Raglan George, Jr., 1973-2002.
    - Correspondence, 1996-1998, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Memoranda, Flyers, 1998, undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Cultural Institutions Retirement System (CIRS), 1995-1998 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Day Care Centers, 1995-1997 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Day Care Council of New York, 1996, undated (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - DC 1707, 1995-1997 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - DC 1707 History, Undated (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Driver License, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Employee Benefits, 1996-1999 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Ephemera, 2002, undated (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Events, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Families and Work Institute, 1993-1995 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Family Day Care, 1991-1995 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Financial, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Fur, Leather and Machine Workers Union-Furriers Joint Council (FLM-FJC)/United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW), 1987-1988 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Grievances/Personnel Issues, 1989-1998 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Grievances--Arbitration Awards, 1981-1985 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Head Start, 1997, undated (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Head Start 70.2 Guidelines, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Head Start Sponsoring Board Council of the City of New York, 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Head Start Sponsoring Board Council of the City of New York--Bargaining, 1982-1998 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Head Start Sponsoring Board Council of the City of New York--Retirement Plan, 1992-1997 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Health and Health Fair, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - High School Intern, 1995, undated (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Human Resources Administration, 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Interim Management Negotiating Committee of Head Start Delegate Agency Boards and Policy Committees--Bargaining, 1979-1981 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Labor History, 1993, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Lawyers Alliance for New York Child Care Law Project, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Legal, 1990-1994 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Local 95 Head Start Employees Welfare Fund, 1996-2000 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Long Island Head Start Child Development Services, 1991-1996 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Long Island Head Start Child Development Services, 1995-1998 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Long Island Head Start Child Development Services--Bargaining, 1992-1999 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Long Island Progressive Coalition, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Meetings/Rallies Permits--Local 95/205, 1995-1999 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Members, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Monthly Reports, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - New York City Administration for Children's Services, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - New York City Central Labor Council, 1991-1999 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - New York City Child Care Budget/Budget Hearing, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - New York City Temporary Task Force on Child Care Funding (I), 1995 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - New York City Temporary Task Force on Child Care Funding (II), 1995 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - New York City Temporary Task Force on Child Care Funding, 1995-1996 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - New York State Senate Assembly, 1997-1998 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Progressive Action Caucus/Committee for a Fair Licensing Procedure (National Teachers Exam), 1995-1996 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Same Boat Coalition, 1996-1997, undated (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Sexual Harassment, 1996-1997 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Socolar, Sandy, 1995-2000 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Staff Activity Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Staff Activity Reports, 1999-2001 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Staff Activity Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Staff Vacations, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Universal Prekindergarten Program, 1997-1998 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Welfare Reform/Welfare Reform Network Child Care Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - White House Conference on Early Childhood, 1997, undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Workfare Organizing, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Working Together for Kids/Worthy Wage Day, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Worthy Wage Campaign, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Subseries IV:C: Josephine LeBeau,1994-2001.
    This subseries contains a small amount of material from Josephine LeBeau, DC 1707 Executive Director from 1994 to 2002. Previous roles within the Council included Staff Representative and Director of Local 389. LeBeau was also involved with the Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW).
    - Addie Wyatt Award, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Clippings, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - General Administrative, 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Highbridge Advisory Council Unfair Labor Practice Charge, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Homes for the Homeless Lawsuit, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Local 205 Awards Dinner, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Newmark and Company Real Estate, 1995-1996 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Notices, Notes, 1999, undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Professional Staff Employees Union, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Tyler, G.L.--Reports, Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Subseries IV:D: Robert McEnroe, 1982-1994.
    McEnroe served as Executive Director of DC 1707 from 1984 to 1994. Files in this subseries pertain to organizing, conferences, and administrative activities.
    - AFSCME: Council Listings, 1985, undated (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - AFSCME Employees Salary Savings Plan, 1985-1993 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Day Care Providers, 1986-1989 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Dues Increase, 1984-1987 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Dues Increase--AFSCME Minimum Dues Increase, 1987-1993 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Family and Medical Leave Act (FMLA), 1993 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - General Administrative, 1985-1992 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - General Administrative, 1993, undated (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Health and Insurance Fund, 1985-1991 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Health Force, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Hudson Decision (I), 1986-1993 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Hudson Decision (II), 1986-1993 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Labor Organization Annual Reports (LM-2 Forms), 1985-1993 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Leadership Conference, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Leadership Conference, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Leadership Conference, 1991, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Lease, 1986-1992 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Legal: Leonard Leibowitz, 1991-1993 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Montalbano Initiatives Inc., 1990-1993 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - M.S. Thesis, Industrial Labor Relations: "A Study in the Evolution of Unionization Among Social Service and Community Organization Workers in New York City During the Period 1930 Thru 1960", Jun 1988 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), 1985-1991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Organizing, 1991-1994 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Organizing: Flyers, Handouts, 1993-1994, undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Organizing: Nassau, Suffolk Counties, 1982-1987 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Organizing: New York State (Upstate) (I), 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Organizing: New York State (Upstate) (II), 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Organizing/Agencies: New York State (Upstate), 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Organizing/Agencies: New York State (Upstate), "AFSCME for Report", 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Organizing Grant, AFSCME, 1984-1993 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Per Capita Tax Payments, 1986-1993 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Puerto Rican Association for Community Affairs: Jurisdictional Dispute with Local 1199, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Safety and Health, 1986-1991 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Staff Conference, Dec 1992 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Subseries IV:E: Richard Morton, 1971-1984.
    One file of administrative material. Morton was Executive Director of Local 1707/DC 1707 from 1970 to 1984.
    - General Administrative, 1971-1984 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Subseries IV:F: Betty Powell, 1988-1999.
    Powell serves as Local 95 President (circa 1990s-present) and as DC 1707 Treasurer (circa 1999-present). Much of the material in this small subseries pertains to Local 95.
    - AFSCME, 1998, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Benefits, 1996, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1997, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU), 1995, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Conferences, 1994-1996 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - DC 1707, 1992-1999 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - DC 1707 Executive Board, 1996-1999 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Domestic Violence, 1995-1996 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Financial Records, 1997-1999 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Flyers, Ephemera, 1997-1999, undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Head Start, 1988-1992 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Head Start: Personnel Issues, 1991-1996 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Local 95, 1991-1999 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Local 95 Executive Board, 1992-1997 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Local 95 Executive Board, 1995-1996 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund (I), 1993-1996 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund (II), 1993-1996 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Local 95 Negotiations, 1996-1997 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - New York City Central Labor Council, 1996-1997 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Notes, Meeting Minutes, 1992-1999, undated (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Reports, 1997-1998, undated (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Subseries IV:G: Brenda Stokely, 1982-2004.
    Stokely served as President of DC 1707 (circa 2002-2004) and as Local 215 President. Much of the material in this subseries relates to Local 215 and its agencies, especially the New York Association for New Americans (NYANA), where Stokely was a shop steward. Items also document Stokely's activity or general interests in labor, politics and political protests.
    - AFL-CIO, 1996, undated (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Agencies, 1999-2000 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Agencies, 2000, undated (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Agencies: Bargaining/Grievances/Personnel (Local 215), 1997-1999 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Agencies: Bargaining/Grievances/Personnel (Local 215), 1997-2000 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Agencies: Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Agencies: Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS), 1994-1995 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Agencies: Grievances/Personnel (Local 215), 1993-1996 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Agencies: Grievance, 1994-1996 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Agencies: Grievance, 1995-1999 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Agencies: Grievances, 1996-1998 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Agencies: Grievances, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Agencies: Grievance--Isaac Ovadiah, 1994-1995 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Benefits, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Class Action Case, 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Committees/Actions, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Contracts, 1996-2000 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 1987-2003 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 1990-1997 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 1996-2003 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 1997-2003 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 1998-2002 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 2001-2003 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 2001-2003 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 2001-2004 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Grievances, 1996-2003 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Grievances, 2000-2002 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Grievance, Brenda Stokely, 1994-1995 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Health Benefits, 1999, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Negotiations (I), 1999 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Negotiations (II), 1999 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Sexual Harassment, 1996-2004 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1997-2000 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Benefit Information, 1982-1997 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Black Workers for Justice, 1991-1996 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Case Assignments, 1997-1998 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Clippings, Articles, 1992-1999 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU): Youth Committee/General, 1995-1999 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Community Resources, Undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence/Memoranda, 1997-2004 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - CSAE Federal Credit Union, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - DC 1707 General Administrative, 1995-1997 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - DC 1707 General Administrative, 1997-1998 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - DC 1707 General Administrative, 1997-2004 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - DC 1707 General Administrative, 2002-2003 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - DC 1707 General Administrative, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Educational Alliance, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Ephemera, 1997-1999, undated (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Family and Medical Leave Act (FMLA), 1994-1996 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Flyers/Circulars/Leaflets, 1997-2004, undated (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Funding/Grant Information, Undated (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Hardship, 1998, undated (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Health and Safety Training, 1998, undated (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Labor/Black History, Undated (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Labor/General, 2000, undated (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Labor Party/New York Labor History, 1997-2003 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Labor Party/New York Labor Party, 2000. undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Labor Resources, 1997, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Local 215 Education Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Local 215 General Administrative, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Local 215 General Administrative, 1997-1999 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Local 215 General Administrative (bulk Little Flower), 1997-1999 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Negotiation Notes, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Neuro-Linguistic Programming (NLP), Undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - New York City Central Labor Council, 1997-1999 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - New York State AFL-CIO, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Notes/Meeting Notes, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Notes/Meeting Notes, 1999-2000, undated (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Organizing, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Politics/Protests, 1995-2003 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Professional, CSW, 1991-1997 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Queens College Worker Education Extension Center Graduation, 1990-1997 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Shop Steward Notes, Undated (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Strike Flyers/Information, 1994, undated (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Workplace Violence Prevention, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Floppy disk: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA), Undated (Box 47)
  - Subseries IV:H: G.L. Tyler, 1991-2001.
    Tyler's titles at DC 1707 include Director of Organizing and Political Action, and Political Action Director (circa 2004). His files mostly relate to organizing and to specific agencies.
    - Allen Health Care Services, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Alpha Kappa Alpha Day Care Center, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Bryan Home Care, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Center for Employment Opportunities, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Central Brooklyn Coordinating Council, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - DC 1707 Political Action Liaison Program, Undated (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Ferncliff Manor for the Retarded, Inc., 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Grievances, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Home Assistance Personnel, Inc., 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Labor-Religion Coalition, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Little Flower Children's Services, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Living Resources, 1997-1999, undated (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Local 205, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Masterson's Day Care Center, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Metro New York Health Care, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), 1995-2001 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Organizing (I), 1997-1999 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Organizing (II), 1997-1999 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Organizing Campaign Manuals, 1998, undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Pine Street Day Care Center, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Rena's Residence for Adults, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Res-Care, Inc., 1998 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Right to Join a Union, Undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Saint Christopher's-Jennie Clarkson Child Care Services, Inc., 1998 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Special Citizens Futures Unlimited, 1997-2000 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Staff Performance Evaluation Forms, Undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Strategic Planning, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Tiny Towne Child Care Center, Inc., 1991-1993 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Union Contract Handout, Undated (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Urban Family Health, 1997-1998 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - US HomeCare, 1998, undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Venture Day Treatment Center/Camp Venture, 1997-1999 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Series V: Publications and Publicity Files, 1982-2004
  Files contain research notes for and drafts of articles, presumably for publication in DC 1707 Voice or Council newsletters. Subjects include DC 1707's agencies, politics, issues of interest to Council members, and profiles of members. Also included are drafts of columns written by DC 1707 and AFSCME officers. Also included in this series are 199 floppy disks, which appear to contain articles, drafts, photos and graphics for DC 1707 publications.
  - Albany: La Salle Academy, Hope House, 2002, undated (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Allen Home Health Care, 2000-2003, undated (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 2004 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - AFSCME: Women the Force of the Future Conference, Undated (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - AFSCME New York State: Lobby Day, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - AMIT, Undated (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Andrew Freeman Home, 2002, undated (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Articles, [1982-1983] (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Articles, [1984], undated (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Articles and Columns, 2002-2004, undated (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Articles and Columns: DC 1707 and AFSCME Officers, 2002, undated (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Beck Notice, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Organization, Local 107, 2003, undated (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Cargill, Undated (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Caring Community, Inc., 2003 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Cartoons, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Cintas, 2004, undated (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Coca-Cola Colombia, 2003, undated (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Condolences, 2004, undated (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Correctional Services Corp, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Day Care, 2004, undated (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Day Care Voice Newsletter, 2004, undated (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - DC 1707, 2003-2004, undated (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - DC 1707 Summit, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Earned Income Tax Credit, Undated (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Education Department Program/Education, 2003, undated (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Election, 2004: Compassion Action (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Election, 2004: Editorial (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Election, 2004: New Hampshire (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Events and Services, 2003, undated (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Services (FEGS), 2003, undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Fields, C. Virginia--Manhattan Borough President, Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Financial Documents, 2004, undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Flyers, [1986], [2003-2004] (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Front Page, 2002, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - George Jr., Raglan: Letter to New York Times, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Grievance Training, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Grievances/Arbitration Awards, 2002-2004, undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Hands Across America, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Head Start, 2002-2003, undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Home Attendants Personnel Inc., 2002-2004 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Home Care, 2004, undated (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Home Care Employees/Homemakers, 2003-2004 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Homecoming, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Hyatt Hotels, Undated (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Immigrant Rights, 2003, undated (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Institute of International Education, Undated (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - International Rescue Committee, 2002, undated (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Iraq War Protests, Undated (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children's Services (JBFCS), Undated (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Jewish Community Centers Metrowest, 2003, undated (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Labor Day, 2003-[2004] (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Latino Affairs Committee, [2003] (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Leake and Watts, 2003, undated (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Lexington Children's Center, 2004, undated (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Living Wage Hearing, 2002, undated (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Local 205, 2002, undated (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Local 205 Bake Sale, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Local 215, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Local 389 Financial Reports, 2002, undated (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Long Island Head Start, Undated (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Louise Wise Services, 2004, undated (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Low Memorial Child Care Center, 2003, undated (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Madison Square Garden Protest, 2004, undated (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - McEnroe Memorial Meeting, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - McMillan/Tart Indictment, 2003, undated (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Metrocare Home Services, 2002-2003 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Mid-Westchester Jewish Community Center, Scarsdale, Undated (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Million Worker March, [2004] (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Legal Defense Fund, 2004, undated (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - New York Society for the Deaf, 2003-2004, undated (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - 92nd St. YM and YWHA, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Organizing, Undated (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Organizing Training, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - Paul J. Cooper Center for Human Services, 2004, undated (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Pleasantville Cottage School, Undated (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - Political Action, 2004, undated (Box 43, Folder 47)